# Shamim Ahmed

## Fullstack Developer

Gollamari, Sonadanga Bypass Rd

Khulna, Bangladesh +8801876082156

Gmail: <a href="mailto:rianahmedshamim99apk@gmail.com">rianahmedshamim99apk@gmail.com</a> Github: <a href="mailto:https://github.com/shamim99apk">https://github.com/shamim99apk</a>



#### INTRODUCTION

I'm a highly self-motivated Web Developer who spends most of his time building applications, implementing highly-responsive user interface components by deploying React concepts and writing application interface code via JavaScript and ReactJS workflows, and also had previous experience working on WordPress. Interested in continuation of learning and cooperation with excellent people.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

DevLeaders, Khulna- Frontend developer

October 2020 - January 2021

- Identified web-based user interactions and developed highly-responsive user interface components
- Developed and implemented front-end architecture to support user interface concepts
- Code Debugging & Front-end Architecture

#### Freelance Web developer, Khulna- Web developer

December 2019 - August 2020

- Created features to enhance the user experience while ensuring that the web design is optimized for smartphones
- Building Websites using Reactjs and Nodejs workflows.
- Employed a variety of languages such as HTML and CSS to write & create user-friendly web pages
- Built reusable code for future use and optimized web pages

maximum speed.

#### **SKILLS**

- Javascript
- React.js
- Redux
- Html5
- CSS3
- Node.js
- Graphql
- Sass
- NoSQL
- C
- Wordpress

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **B.Sc in Computer Science and Engineering**

North Western University, Khulna

February 2019 - Present

#### **Higher Secondary School Certificate (HSC)**

Government Sundarban Adarsha College, Khulna

2016 - 2018

#### **PROJECTS**

• E-commerce app with Payment gateway and Admin

### Dashboard using MERN Stack

https://etcshopbd.herokuapp.com/

React 17 projects
<a href="https://github.com/shamim99apk/17-react-projects">https://github.com/shamim99apk/17-react-projects</a>

• E-commerce app using React.js and firebase

https://crowneshop.netlify.app/

• Custom Landing Page using Html5 and CSS3

https://insurange-rian.netlify.app/ https://bussinessplus.netlify.app/ https://bestuilandingpage.netlify.app/